Guide to the Cutberto Garza papers, [ca. 1989-2009]
Garza, Cutberto papers, [ca. 1989-2009]
- ICSU Workshop - Working Paper - Genetically Modified Foods for Human Health and Nutrition, May 2002 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Genetically Modified Organisms (GMOs) - Health Effects - Papers, Memos, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- USDA Advisory Board - Correspondence - National Agricultural Research, Extension, Education, and Economics Advisory Board, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- USDA - National Agricultural Research, Extension, Education, and Economics Advisory Board - Correspondence, Memos, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- USDA - National Agricultural Research, Extension, Education, and Economics Advisory Board - Correspondence, Memos, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- NCI - Nutrition Subcommittee of the Board of Scientific Counselors, 1982-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Dannon Institute - BOD meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Macy Foundation - Planning Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Macy Foundation - Conferences, 1999, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- U.S. Dietary Guidelines - Advisory Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- U.S. Dietary Guidelines - Advisory Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Dietary Guidelines - Publications, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- United Nations University - Subcommittee on Nutrition, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Alcohol Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Fat Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Food Safety Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Grain Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Weight Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 16)
- General Dietary Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Physical Activity Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Salt Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Sugar Guidelines, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- International Auxology Congress - England, July 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NIH Meeting/Talk - "Role of Human Milk in HIV Infection", February 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Richard Theuer - Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Talk - Agency for International Development, February 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Lecture - Spiegel Foundation - Columbia, April 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Workshop - Nutritional Problems in Children in the Developing World - CA, June 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Experiment Station Committee on Organization and Policy (ESCOP) Symposium - Washington, D.C., June 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Talk - Pediatric Grand Rounds - New York City - "Infant Feedings", 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Advisory Workshop on Issues in Nutrition Research - MD, November 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Lecture - International Nutrition-Class NS680 - Infant Feeding, October 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Talk - March of Dimes - Texas, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Chapter - Susskind's Book, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- New York State Dietetic Association Annual Meeting - Saratoga Springs, May 1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- American Institute of Nutrition, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Joint Council / Food and Agricultural Science - Illinois, January 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- World Food Program, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- World Food Program, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Mead Johnson Symposium - Indiana, May 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- International Congress of Nutrition - XV - Workshop 53 - "Nutrition in Pregnancy and Lactation", September 1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- International Congress of Nutrition - XV - Australia, September 26-October 1, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- USDA Roundtable - Washington, D.C., June 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- WHO / Wellstart Tech Consultation - Washington, July 1994 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- WHO / Wellstart Tech Consultation - Washington, July 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Food and Agriculture Organization - U.N. - San Antonio, August 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- UNICEF Colloquium - October 1994; Poly Prevention Trial (PPT) Data and Safety Monitoring Committee, November 1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Panel Discussion, November 6, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- International Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Congressional File, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Senator Lugar - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Report of the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee on the Dietary Guidelines for Americans and Comments, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- International Union of Nutritional Sciences - Bangkok, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- USDA Dietary Guidelines - Working Group, February 1996 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Public Nutrition Consortium, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- WHO - World Alliance for Breastfeeding Action, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- WHO - Nutrition Unit - proposals, correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- WHO - Growth Reference - 2nd phase, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- WHO - Growth Reference - 2nd phase, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- WHO - Growth Reference - 2nd phase, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Dietary Guidelines Publications, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Dietary Guidelines Publications, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Dietary Guidelines Publications, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Dietary Guidelines -Correspondence, Memos, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Dietary Guidelines -Correspondence, Memos - 2 folders, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting, September 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting - 2 folders, September 1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Oral Testimony, March 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Oral Testimony - 2 folders, March 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Briefing Book, June 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Briefing Book - 2 folders, June 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee, June 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - 2 folders, June 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - 3 folders, June 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - 4th meeting, September 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - 4th meeting, September 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting, September 1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting - 2 folders, September 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting - 3 folders, September 1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting - September 1999 (4) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting - 5 folders, September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting, September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting, September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee Meeting, September 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Summary of recommendations from public comments, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries - Dr. Shanty Bowman, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries - (samples), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries (samples), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries (samples), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries (samples), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning alcohol, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning supplements, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning carbohydrates, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning food safety, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning lipids, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning obesity, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Commentaries concerning sodium, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Dannon Institute Board, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Economic Research Service - Conference, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- New York State Community Health Partnership, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New York State Community Health Partnership, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- New York State Community Partnership, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- New York State Community Partnership, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Nestle Nutrition Scholarship Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Marabou Symposium, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Session Papers - USDA Conference - "Toward Convergence on the Dietary Guidelines: Research and Policy Needs", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Session Papers - USDA Conference - "Toward Convergence on the Dietary Guidelines: Research and Policy Needs", October 1998 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee - Discussion of proposed changes, January 2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Dietary Guidelines for Americans - Final draft, January 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- WHO - Briefing - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", October 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- WHO - Briefing - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", October 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- WHO - Briefing - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- WHO - Manuscripts from the Growth Analyses, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", November 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", November 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", November 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- WHO - Expert Committee on "Physical Status: The Use and Interpretation of Anthropometry", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- WHO - Working Group on Growth Reference Protocol, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- WHO - Working Group on Growth Reference Protocol, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- WHO - A Growth Curve for the 21st Century - Protocol, June 1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Meeting, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Meeting, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Meeting, September 1998 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Third Steering Committee Meeting, October 1999 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Third Steering Committee Meeting, October 1999 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Third Steering Committee Meeting, October 1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Plan of Analysis, Data Report, Motor Development Assessment, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Interviewer's Guide, Questionnaires (Box 17, Folder 2)
- WHO- Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Analyzing Documents, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Longitudinal Study Progress Report; Plan of Analysis of two HRP Studies, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study Guides (Box 17, Folder 5)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Methods for Contruction of the Growth References, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study, April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study -Ad Hoc Statistical Advisory Group, January 2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Supporting Letters for Proposal, October 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Papers and Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Child Growth Standards, March 2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Child Growth Standards, March 2005 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- WHO - Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Supplement, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- WHO- Multicentre Growth Reference Study - Principal Investigators Meeting, March 2010 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- World Food Program - "Time for Change: Food Aid and Development" - background papers, October 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- World Food Program - "Time for Change: Food Aid and Development" - background papers, October 1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- WHO - Data Management Monitoring Report, December 2000 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Articles, Memos, Letters of Inquiry, Agreements - Concerning Infant Formula, Zambia, WHO violence report, International Growth Standards for Infants, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- ICSU, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Pre-SCN Capacity Building Workshop- South Africa, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Joint WHO/FAO/UNU Expert Consultation on Protein and Amino Acid Requirements in Human Nutrition, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Joint WHO/FAO/UNU Expert Consultation on Protein and Amino Acid Requirements in Human Nutrition, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Joint WHO/FAO/UNU Expert Consultation on Protein and Amino Acid Requirements in Human Nutrition, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Standing Committee on Nutrition, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- WHO Sugar Intake Recommendations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Infant Formula Subcommittee of the Food and Drug Administration, November 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Middle East File, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Joint WHO/FAO Workshop "A Model for Establishing Upper Levels of Intake for Nutrients and Related Substances, May 2005 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Joint WHO/FAO Workshop "A Model for Establishing Upper Levels of Intake for Nutrients and Related Substances, May 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- FAO/WHO Nutrient Risk Assessment Workshop, May 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Dietary Harmonization Meeting, December 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Dietary Harmonization Meeting, December 2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Cornell Files, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Chapter by Garza in "The Nations Nutrition", 2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Oncology Articles (Box 18, Folder 9)
- School Age Growth References, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Mohamed Ag Ayoya - Letters, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Reviews of Chapters/Papers by Garza, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- WHO emails, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- International Growth Standard Meeting, January 2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- International Growth Standard Meeting, January 2006 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Multicentre Growth Reference Study (MGRS) Maternal Weight Change Report, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 16)